Sam Gejdenson Papers 2001.0008
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, undated, 1966-2001
  - Press Clippings, Press Releases, undated, 1985-2000 (Box 123)
    - American Trim closes, 1990
    - Environment, undated, 1990
    - United Nations Delagate, 1990
    - State of the Union, undated, 1990
    - Plant Closing, undated, 1989-1990
    - Diversification, undated, 1988-1990
    - Electric Boat cuts, undated, 1990
    - Foreign Trade, undated, 1990
    - Economy, undated, 1989-1990
    - Budget and Taxes, undated, 1990
    - General files, 1985-2000
    - Credit Elsewhere Test, 1985-1989
  - Native Americans and other legislative files, undated, 1950, 1971-1990 (Box 124)
    - House Resolution 1646, Indian Burial Protection Act, 1950, 1989
    - House Resolution1506, Black Hills Act, 1987
    - House Resolution 73, Amateur Radio, 1989
    - Flag desecration, 1989-1990
    - Internal Revenue Service, $600 Conservation Ruling, 1989
    - Spectrum Protection Act, 1991
    - Internal Revenue Service Regulations, 1989-1990
    - Ship Building, 1989
    - Department of Energy, Alaska n Natural Gas Utility Rate Payer Refund Act of 1987, 1986-1987
    - Education of the Handicapped Act, 1989
    - Sharp, Clean Air Proposal, 1990
    - McKinney Homeless Grants, 1989
    - Television Regulations, 1989
    - Pequot Gambling, 1989-1991
    - Mashantucket Pequot LDAG Appropiations, 1989
    - Mashantucket Pequot, 1983-1989
    - Whistleblower Protection, 1989-1990
    - Religious Broadcasting, 1988
    - Hopi/Navajo, 1971-1990
    - Native American Legislation, 1990-1991
    - Mashantucket Pequot, Payment in Lieu of Taxes, 1991
    - Shaping Our own Future: Native American Self-Governance, 1989-1991
    - Cherokee Nation, 1988-1990
    - Mohegans, 1989
    - Seminole Judgement, 1989-1990
    - Final Report: Indian Land Claims Study, undated
    - Federal Communications Commission, Computer Rates, 1987
    - Reed's Letter to Aspin, 1993
    - Veterans' Conference, 1995
  - Health Care, undated, 1996-2000 (Box 125)
    - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO)/Medicare Admistrative Costs, 1998-2000
    - Health Care, 1997-1998
    - Medicare/HMOs 141, 1997-2000
    - Cancer, 1998
    - Yale Child Study Center, 1999
    - HMO Reform, 1998-2000
    - Women's Health Conference, 2000
    - Health Fairs, 1996-1998
    - University of Connecticut's Regional Medical Library, undated
    - Tourettes, 1999-2000
    - West Nile Virus, 1999-2000
    - Health Reform, 1998-2000
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, photographs, publications, 1994-2000 (Box 126)
    Scope and Content Note
    [Subjects include: Connecticut research, flight safety, juvenile crime, federal prison, U.S. Department of Justice, violence against women]
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 127)
    [Subjects include: Legislation concerning Medicare, health, housing, transportation, Native Americans.]
  - Administrative records, clippings(photocopied), correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 128)
    [Subjects include: Finance reform campaign, Healthcare reform, Seawolf.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, legal documents, notes, 1981-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 129)
    [Subjects include: Foreign aid, international affairs, Iran-Contra arms scandal.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, legal documents, notes, map, 1987-1988 (Box 130)
    [Subjects: Legislation concerning Tongass National Forrest.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, legal documents, 1990-1991 (Box 131)
    [Subjects include: Arms legislation, Gulf War, United Nations.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 132)
    [Subjects include: U.S. submarines, Electric Boat, Seawolf.]
  - Clippings, publications, 1984 (Box 133)
    [Subjects include: Off-shore drilling, State of the Union, ’84 tax bill.]
  - Correspondence, financial records, publications, 1986-1989 (Box 134)
    [Subjects include: House bills, Korean memorial, press releases.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1989-1991 (Box 135)
    [Subjects include: Arms transfers, foreign policy, hostages in Iran, International Court, NATO terrorism.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 136)
    [Subjects include: GAO, Foreign Assets Control, Somalia Human Rights.]
  - Administrative records, 1985-1990 (Box 137)
    [Subjects include: Foreign Policy.]
  - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 138)
    [Subjects include: DEP, Dodd Stadium, OceanQuest, Pequot Tribe, UConn.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, legal documents, 1987-1992 (Box 139)
    [Subjects include: Foreign policy, human rights, Iran-Contra Affair, immigration policy, reproductive rights.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, 1990-1994 (Box 140)
    [Subjects: Mohegan Agreement, Mohegan Tribe and Casino Plan.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, 1991-1992 (Box 141)
    [Subjects include: Defense Workers Bill, conferences, Pequot Casino Plan, tourism, trade, unemployment.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 142)
    [Subjects include: Foreign policy (general/human rights), Ocean Freight Reimbursement Program.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1989, 1990-1991 (Box 143)
    [Subjects include: Budget, economy and trade.]
  - Administrative records, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, 1987-1989 (Box 144)
    [Subjects include: George Bush & Ronald Reagan, Panama conflict/Contras.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, notes, publications, 1995-2001 (Box 145)
    [Subjects: Air Force, defense, military .]
  - House Journal, 1979, 1980, 1981, 1985, 1989 (Box 146)
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 147)
    [Subjects include: Cambodia n refugees, development in Central America, foreign affairs, terrorism.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, 1995-2000 (Box 148)
    [Subjects include: Defense, Seawolf, subs, technology, U.S. Navy, 100 year sub celebration.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, 1985 (Box 149)
    [Subjects include: Electric Boat, naval security, submarines, U.S. Navy.]
  - Video cassettes (11), 1985 (Box 150)
    [Subjects include: Ask Congress.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1984-1985 (Box 151)
    [Subjects: Campaign, Holocaust, home-based businesses, outreach to women, Peace Corps, voting.]
  - Audio cassettes (5), Video cassettes (20), 1982-1983 (Box 152)
    [Subjects include: Defense, economy, interviews, News from Congress.]
  - Clippings, publications, 1993-1995 (Box 153)
    [Subjects include: Foxwoods Casino, Mashantucket Pequots, Nuclear plant, Millstone, Pequot Times.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, publications, 1993-1995 (Box 154)
    [Subjects include: US Nuclear Regulatory Commission.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 155)
    [Subjects include: Campaign, contras, flooding, Nuclear weapons, tax reform, waste.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 156)
    [Subjects include: Recycling.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, notes, publications, 1985-1995 (Box 157)
    [Subjects include: Healthcare, radioactive waste, Social Security.]
  - Administrative, correspondence, notes, publications, 1998-2000 (Box 158)
    [Subjects include: Defense, National Guard, Navy, Pratt & Whitney, research and development, United Technologies.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, legal documents, 1988-1990 (Box 159)
    [Subjects include: Committee of Interior and Insular Affairs.]
  - Administrative records, legal documents, publications, 1986-1991 (Box 160)
    [Subjects include: Land and Water Conservation Fund, Long Island Sound conservation, Marine conservation, oil spill prevention, Weir Far.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, transcripts, 1985-1988 (Box 161)
    [Subjects include: foreign affairs, Haiti an Dental Foundation, Kuwait hijacking, travel.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, legal documents, notes, transcripts, 1982, 1984-1987,1989, 1990 (Box 162)
    [Subjects include: Defense, economic conversion.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, publications (articles), 1992-1996 (Box 163)
    [Subjects include: Animal rights, broadcasting, education, energy and environmental policy, health, Social Security, veterans, welfare.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications (articles), transcripts, 1991-1992 (Box 164)
    [Subjects include: Economy and trade, China debate, energy, healthcare, tax income, UConn, unemployment.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, publications (articles), 1985 (Box 165)
    [Subjects include: Budget, education, energy and environmental policy, financial aid, foreign aid/policy, Nicaragua (Contras), social security, veterans.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, photographs, publications (articles), reports, transcripts, 1984, 1988-1989, 1990-1991 (Box 166)
    [Subjects include: Aviation ( U.S. Air Force, Marine Corps), defense, nuclear war.]
  - Photographs, Sound Recordings (4 cassette tapes), Moving images (32 video cassettes), 1986, 1988-1989, 1990, 1992- 1994, 1996 (Box 167)
    [Subjects include: Gejdenson for Congress, Gejdenson Reelection Committee.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, reports, transcripts, 1991-1993, 1995 (Box 168)
    [Subjects include: Defense Base Closure and Realignment Committee, Groton Submarine Base, U.S. Navy.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, reports, 1991-1997 (Box 169)
    [Subjects include: Defense Base Closure and Realignment Committee, Groton Submarine Base, Seawolf, U.S. Navy.]
  - Books (24), 1988, 1991-1993, 1996-1998 (Box 170)
    [Subjects include: Economics, foreign relations, family/friendship, politics.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, reports, 1983-1998 (Box 171)
    [Subjects include: Defense Base Closure and Realignment, EPA, highway/route development, NUWC, Seawolf, U.S. Navy.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, flyers, maps, reports, 1986-1988, 1990-1996 (Box 172)
    [Subjects include: Historic preservation in CT, National Park Service, tourism, U.S. Census Bureau.]
  - Books (19), 1989, 1990-1991, 1994-1995 (Box 173)
    [Subjects include: Economics, health.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, legal documents, transcripts, 1994 (Box 174)
    [Subjects include: 1994 election recount, voting.]
  - Books (6), 1993-1994 (Box 175)
    [Subjects include: Committee on Foreign Affairs Vol. 6-11.]
  - Books (10), 1993-1994 (Box 176)
    [Subjects include: Committee on Foreign Affairs Vol. 21-30.]
  - Books (6), 1993-1994 (Box 177)
    [Subjects include: Committee on Foreign Affairs Vol.1-5, Committee Calendar.]
  - Book (8), Dates: Organization: N/A, 1993-1994 (Box 178)
    [Subjects include: Committee on Foreign Affairs Vol. 13-20.]
  - Books (8), 1993-1994 (Box 179)
    [Subjects include: Committee on International Relations Vol. 6-13.]
  - Books (7), 1993-1996 (Box 180)
    [Subjects include: Committee on Foreign Affairs Vol.31-32, Committee on International Relations Vol. 1-5.]
  - Books (10), 1995-1996 (Box 181)
    [Subjects include: Committee on International Relations Vol. 14-23.]
  - Books (10), 1995-1996 (Box 182)
    [Subjects include: Committee on International Relations Vol. 24-33.]
  - Moving images (12 U-matic video cassettes), 1995 (Box 183)
    [Subjects include: Electric Boat, Norwichtown Mall, seniors, veterans, Willimantic.]
  - Moving images (28 video cassettes), 1986, 1992, 1997, 2000 (Box 184)
    [Subjects include: Sam Gejdenson for Congress.]
  - Moving images (4, U-matic video cassettes, 4 video tapes/recordings) Sound recordings (4 7.5 IPS tape recordings, 1 15 IPS tape recording, 3 other 30-second tape recordings), 1982, 1990 (Box 185)
    [Subjects include: Campaigning, Sam Gejdenson for Congress, radio interviews.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, 1997 (Box 186)
    [Subjects include: Natural resources, Native Americans, Social Security, transportation, tourism women’s issues.]
  - Legal records, transcripts, 1994 (Box 187)
    [Subjects include: 1994 Reelection recount .]
  - Moving images (3 video recordings/tapes, 22 VHS tapes) Optical disks (2 CD-ROM, 1 floppy disk), Sound recording (17 cassette tapes), 1989, 1990, 1992, 1994, 1996, 1998, 2000 (Box 188)
  - Clippings, fliers, realia (stickers), 1979, 1981-1982, 1984, 1996 (Box 189)
    [Subjects include: Sam Gejdenson for Congress, voting.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, publications, reports, transcripts, 1981- 2001 (Box 190)
    [Subjects include: Environmental policy, Gejdenson Record, Groton, Pfizer, Sam Gejdenson for Congres.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, legal documents, transcripts, 1992, 1994, 2000 (Box 191)
    [Subjects include: 1994 election recount, 2000 election defeat.]
  - Books (22), 1984, 1989, 1995, 1999 (Box 192)
    [Subjects include: International relations, ecology/environmental science, medicine, politics.]
  - Optical disks (1 CD-ROM, 1 micro-floppy disk, 2 mini-floppy disks), moving images (3 VHS tapes, 8 VR tapes), 1982, 1984, 1992, 1998 (Box 193)
    [Subjects include: Gejdenson Reelection Committee, Sam Gejdenson for Congress.]